《生活大爆炸》前情提要
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
我也不需要纠结这事
There's no point in dwelling on it.
借用一句瓦肯人的俗语
As the Vulcans say,
"人已杀  你无力还命"[瓦肯语]
"Kup-fun-tor ha'kiv na'ish du stau."
-你懂他的意思吗  -不懂
- Do you know what that means? - No.
你说的是实话吗
Are you telling the truth?
非也[瓦肯语]
Nersh.
这一切都太荒唐了  总是为艾米的事伤心
This is ridiculous-- being upset about Amy all the time
不能解决任何问题
isn't accomplishing anything.
如果我想解决这件事
If I want to resolve this situation,
我就要行动起来
then I need to take action.
你要干什么
What are you gonna do?
我要去找她  向她求婚
I'm going to find her and ask her to marry me.
如果她答应了
And if she says yes,
我们就把这事彻底忘掉  重新开始
we can put this behind us and resume our relationship.
如果她不肯答应
And if she says no...
那她就可以去自尽了[瓦肯语]
well, then she can just ponfo miran.
他不是真心的
He didn't mean that.
你帮谢尔顿做早饭真是太有爱了
I think it's so adorable you're making Sheldon breakfast.
他现在很难过嘛
Well, he's having a rough time.
艾米伤了他的心
Amy broke his heart,
录《神秘博士》时录少了最后一分钟
the DVR cut off the last minute of Doctor Who...
回家时还被乌鸦跟踪
that crow followed him home.
你不怕在燕麦粥日做法式吐司会出事吗
Aren't you worried you're making French toast on oatmeal day?
你看这是啥  不就是一锅燕麦粥吗
Ah, well, what's this? A pot of oatmeal?
或者应该谢谢你  改称它为"我真牛逼粥"
Or, thanks to you, what I will now call "Gloatmeal."
我可不想跟它沾边
Oh, I don't want credit for that.
霍夫斯塔德博士贤伉俪
Oh, Dr. And Mrs. Hofstadter,
在这美好的早晨很高兴见到两位
lovely to see you this fine morning.
你心情很好啊
You're in a good mood.
的确是的
Yeah, I am indeed.
我已经决定了
I have decided,
与其为艾米的事伤神伤心
instead of wallowing in sadness about Amy,
不如抓紧时间为自己找个新女伴
it is time that I find myself a new female companion.
那挺好啊
Oh. Good for you.
这想法怎么来的
What brought this on?
我意识到了  当艾米在我身边时
I realized something-- when Amy was in my life,
我过度专注于工作而忽略了她
I was hyper-focused on my work and ignored her.
你不想对下一个女人重蹈覆辙
And you don't want to make the same mistake with the next woman.
不  所以我需要一个新女人来被我忽略
No, I need a new woman in my life to ignore
好让我再次过度专注于工作
so I can hyper-focus on my work again.
我做了法式吐司棒
Hey, I made French toast sticks.
燕麦粥日做这个吗
On oatmeal day?
我也做了燕麦粥哦
Ah, I also made oatmeal.
对于要猎艳的男人来说  太容易长胖了
Ooh, that's a lot of carbohydrates for a man on the prowl.
还是你吃吧  你结婚了
You know what? You eat it; you're married--
长成啥样都无所谓了
it doesn't matter what you look like.
千万别听一个用鞋子扔乌鸦的人的建议
Don't take advice from a man who threw his shoe at a crow.
翻译：大变态色色哒赛  小变态萌萌哒猫
猫中之王  别扭大菜
谢谢你们抽空来  先生们
Thank you for coming by, gentlemen.
小意思
No problem.
怎么了
So what's up?
是你们两位为我找到艾米·菲拉·福勒
Well, it was the two of you who found Amy Farrah Fowler for me.
现在我在寻觅我下一任女朋友
Now that I'm looking for my next girlfriend,
所以我觉得
it seemed only logical
只有再度请你们出手才合理
that I employ your services once again.
她伤了你的心  你真的能再战了吗
Y-You sure you're up for that? She did hurt you.
没事的  不算什么
Oh, no, it's all right.
我跟艾米在一起的时光就像水果口香糖
I think of my time with Amy as a stick of Fruit Stripe gum:
一开始甜蜜好滋味
sweet and enjoyable at first,
但最后也只是一团无味的悲哀
but ultimately a flavorless lump of sadness.
用水果口香糖来形容也没错
You're not wrong about Fruit Stripe.
但我向来都比较喜欢胶带泡泡糖
I-I was always a Hubba Bubba man. Mm.
喜欢胶带泡泡糖多过波波泡泡糖吗  你疯啦
Hubba Bubba over Dubble Bubble? You're crazy.
我下巴喜欢嚼哪种就哪种
Hey, the jaw wants what it wants.
两位
Gentlemen!
抱歉  是来说女朋友
Oh, right, uh, girlfriend.
你想找怎么样的呢
But what are you looking for?
我想找一个受过良好教育  非常聪明的女人
All I'm looking for is an educated, intelligent woman
跟我有相同的兴趣爱好
who shares my interests
但同时又有自己的想法与见解
while retaining her own unique point of view.
为人和蔼有耐心
She should be kind, patient,
而且最重要的是
and most important,
在今晚十点前就爱我爱到无法自拔
unable to imagine life without me by 10:00 tonight.
这要求是不是有点不合理
Isn't that a little unreasonable?
好吧  她不需要有自己的想法与见解
All right, fine, she doesn't need her own point of view.
赶紧开工吧
Now, chop-chop.
艾米  快点  让我们看看那裙子
Come on, Amy, show us the dress.
来啦
Okay.
但这真的是超出了我的舒适区
But I'm really stepping outside of my comfort zone here.
你的"舒适区"一点都没有露出来啊
I don't think any of your comfort zones are showing.
都第三次约会了
Yeah, it's your third date--
要不打扮性感点试试
maybe you could go more sexy.
有些人觉得最性感的器官是脑子呢
Well, some people think the sexiest organ is the brain.
但我去酒吧的时候
No one ever bought me drinks at a bar
从来没有人因为我露"脑"而请我喝酒啊
because my brain just popped out of my shirt.
你们有没有高一点的高根鞋
Do you have any heels higher than this?
他个子还挺高
He's pretty tall.
高个子
Ooh, tall!
终于透露了点这位神秘男士的细枝末节了
Finally some details about this mystery man.
继续  再跟我们说说
Yeah, come on, tell us more.
我跟你们说过了他的名字  还有他很高
Well, I told you his name and that he's tall.
你们还需要知道什么啊
What more do you need?
你们接吻没
Did you kiss him yet?
就嘴唇上吻了一下
Just a little peck on the lips.
我们可是好闺蜜  再说一个细节吧
Well, we're your best friends-- give us one more detail
说完保证不再烦你
and we promise we'll leave you alone.
好吧
Fine. Um...
他是英国人
he's British.
好啦  这点的确是很让人兴奋
All right, that is a juicy one.
英国高个子戴夫今晚要带你上哪呢
All right, where is Tall British Dave taking you?
喝茶加打篮球吗
Tea and basketball?
去那家新开的意大利餐厅
To that new Italian place on Walnut.
挺好啊
Oh, nice.
我再去找找别双鞋
I'm gonna go look for other shoes.
加油找吧
Good luck.
嫁给莱纳德时  我把高的高跟鞋全扔了
I threw out all my tall ones when I married Leonard.
你今晚想路过他们的约会地
Hey, you want to swing by that place tonight
看看那男人的庐山真面目吗
and get a look at this guy?
我们都不知道他们约了几点
We don't even know what time they're gonna be there.
我可以打给那个餐厅
I'll just call the restaurant,
假装我是艾米  再确认一下预定时间
pretend I'm Amy and check the reservation.
靠  你真贼
Damn, you're sneaky.
但我人小  做啥都萌萌哒
Yeah, but I'm little, so it's adorable.
我觉得帮你找女朋友最快的方法
I think the quickest way to find you a new girlfriend
就是帮你注册市面上所有的相亲网站
is just to get you on every dating Web site out there.
你确定这有用吗
Are you sure?
我听说在这种网站上  常常会有
I've heard that on those sites, often when you think
你以为自己跟妞儿聊上天了
you're corresponding with someone,
结果只是电脑AI
it's actually a computer program
假装是真人在回你
pretending to be a real person.
你担心电脑AI比你这人形AI会聊天吗
And you're afraid it'll do a better job than you?
不好意思
Excuse me.
假装是人类这件事上  我是打遍天下无敌手
No one does a better job pretending to be a person than I do.
Siri跟我不相上下  但我知道的笑话比它多
Siri comes close, but I know more jokes.
如果你不想用相亲网站
If you don't want to use dating websites,
那你有什么好建议
what do you suggest?
随便一想吗
Off the top of my head?
众多有前瞻性的女性们
Uh, prospective women weed themselves out
靠智斗战胜其他人  最后夺冠的那一个人
in a battle of wits until only one champion remains,
带着胜利的激动  出现在我家门外
she shows up at my door flush with the thrill of victory,
她会在我看《夜魔侠》时
and then sits quietly by my side
默默坐到本皇身边
while I watch Daredevil.
你真的认为女人会为你而战吗
You seriously think women would fight for you?
人们会为了工作和奖杯而战  为啥不会为我
People compete for jobs and trophies-- why not me?
他说得对  他的确知道很多笑话
He's right-- he knows a lot of jokes.
对  不  但这的确是人的本性
Yeah-- no, but it is basic human nature.
如果把他像奖品般呈现  或许真有女人会抢
If we present him as a prize, maybe they would.
他很聪明
Well, he's smart,
又是个受人尊敬的科学家
he's a respected scientist...
而且我有一双深情似水的明眸
And I have the soulful eyes of a cow.
我可不会说你的眼...
I don't know if I'd say you...
我有个主意
I have an idea.
不如我们在分类广告网上发个帖子  就写
What if we put a post on Craigslist that says:
"加州理工学院世界级物理学家征女友一名
"World-class Caltech physicist seeking girlfriend.
如果有兴趣
If interested,
请解出如下谜题  赢取见面机会"
solve the following puzzles for a chance to meet him."
我们要把题出得极有挑战性
Oh, we'll make the puzzles extremely challenging
才能筛掉不合格的候选人
to eliminate unworthy candidates.
我们可以设置得像一个寻宝游戏
Oh, we could set it up like a scavenger hunt
解开最后一道题才能得到谢尔顿的联系方式
where the last puzzle gives the winner Sheldon's contact information.
这真是个有趣的社会实验
Well, this is actually an interesting social experiment.
我有点嫉妒可以参与解谜的人了
I'm a little jealous of the people who get to do it.
我也是
Me, too.
而且我们已经见过这"大奖"了
And we've seen the prize.
我不懂看电影为啥要这么早出门
I don't understand why we're leaving so early for the movie.
我忘了告诉你了  我们要跟伯纳黛特碰面
Oh, I forgot to tell you-- we're gonna meet up with Bernadette
一起监视艾米和她的男伴
to spy on Amy and her date.
什么
What?
我不想做这事情
I don't want to do that.
干嘛  你真以为我会想看
What, and you think I want to see
一部关于铝罐回收的纪录片吗
a documentary about aluminum can recycling?
这可是软饮料行业不想大众去看的电影
This is the movie Big Soda doesn't want you to see.
错  是你老婆不想让你去看
No, it's the movie your wife doesn't want you to see.
你觉得侵犯你朋友的隐私没问题吗
So you're actually okay with invading your friend's privacy?
你不好奇她跟谁约会吗
You're not curious who she's out with?
不太
Not really.
但你却对铝罐有兴趣
But you're curious about aluminum cans.
你真是奇怪的小男人
You're a weird little guy.
好了  谢尔顿·库珀女友挑战赛
That's it. The Sheldon Cooper Girlfriend Challenge
正式上线了
is officially alive.
-恭喜  -太令人激动了
- Congratulations. - This is exciting.
现在在某处
Right now, somewhere,
有一个女人正用
a woman is dividing the atomic weight
沿用至今最古老的国旗上的颜色数量
of the best noble gas by the number of colors
除以惰性最强的气体的原子量
in the oldest national flag still in use...
然后用得出的数作为平均速度
W-- then using that number as the average speed
计算出从魔多到夏尔郡所需的时间
to calculate the travel time from Mordor to the Shire.
还有
And...
向美好的一生迈出第一步
taking her first step towards a lifetime
等着她的将是笑声爱意  以及规矩
of laughter, love and, best of all, rules.
希望我们没有把题出得太难
I-I hope we didn't make the puzzles too hard.
如果她可以解开
Well...if she can solve them,
那将证明她非常聪明
it'll prove she's intelligent,
固执顽强  而且不善社交
tenacious and... so socially awkward
因为周六晚上居然没有更好的事可做
she has nothing better to do on a Saturday night.
天啊  感觉美好得让人难以置信
Golly, she sounds too good to be true.
这样挺好的  我离婚之后没怎么跟人约过会
This is fun. I haven't dated much since my divorce.
我也玩得很开心
Well, I'm having a good time, too.
希望你不介意我这么问
If you don't mind me asking,
你和你妻子为什么离婚
why did you and your wife split up?
你也知道的  我们的追求不一样
Oh, you know how it is-- we wanted different things.
我想要孩子
I wanted children,
她想要一个叫让·菲利普的糕点师
and she wanted a pastry chef named Jean-Philippe.
我深感同情
Oh, I'm... I'm so sorry.
没事的  我就是因此而离开英国
No, it's-it's fine. It's why I left England.
那里有太多事物会让我想起她
It reminded me too much of her.
冷冷的  闷闷的
Cold, gloomy
随便让法国佬从"隧道"进入
and easily accessed by a Frenchman through a tunnel.
他们在哪里
Hey. So, where are they?
对面街的左边窗口
Across the street, in the left window.
靠  我们应该带望远镜来的
Oh, damn it, we should have brought binoculars.
早有准备
Right here.
车里碰巧就有吗
We just happen to have those in the car?
算是吧  我在认识霍华德之前
Kinda. Before I met Howie,
我喜欢密切关注我的男友们
I liked to keep close tabs on my boyfriends.
跟踪他们吗
By stalking them?
不  跟踪狂多变态
No. Stalkers are creepy.
我只是个人畜无害的小女孩
I'm just a harmless little girl
有点军事级别的间谍设备而已
with military-grade spy equipment.
看见他了
Oh, there he is.
他长得还行  对吧
He's cute, right?
对
Yeah!
我能看一下吗
Can I see?
现在你感兴趣了吗  之前都不愿意来
What, now you're interested? You didn't even want to come.
我知道
I know,
但你们让做一个损友变得好有意思
but you guys make being a crappy friend look fun.
好吧
Fine.
好了  我看见他了
Yeah, okay, I see him.
看起来他们聊得挺开心的
It looks like they're having a nice time.
真希望能听见他们在说什么
I wish I could hear what they're saying.
对呀  真该把我的抛物面传声器带来
Yeah, I should've brought my parabolic microphone.
你的什么
Your what?
没什么  不重要
Nothing. Not important.
所以你从来没结过婚
So you've never been married?
没有  但老实说  我...
No. I mean, to be completely honest, I've...
我只谈过一场长期的恋爱
I've only been in one long-term relationship.
出了什么状况
Oh. What happened with that?
这个问题问得非常好
That's a good question.
五年之后
After five years,
这段感情变得太累太沉重了
it was just feeling like more work than it should be.
那可太不幸了
Oh, that's too bad.
他也是神经生物学家吗
Was he a neurobiologist like you?
不  他是加州理工的理论物理学家
No. He's a theoretical physicist at Caltech.
我虽喜欢教数学  可那才是我梦寐以求的工作
I love teaching math, but that would be my dream job.
他的研究方向是什么
What's his focus?
之前是弦理论  现在换成了暗物质
Um... used to be string theory, now it's dark matter.
不过...我们还是不要谈谢尔顿了
But... let's not discuss Sheldon.
还是来谈谈你吧
Let's get back to you.
等等  你说的该不会是谢尔顿·库珀博士吧
Wait, you're not talking about Dr. Sheldon Cooper?
我正努力不提呢
I'm trying not to.
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
不认识  但我关注他的研究很多年了
No, but I've followed his work for years.
他可是学界巨星啊
He's a rock star.
你一定得给我好好说说他
You've got to tell me about him.
他是个什么样的人啊
What's he like?
他看起来相当喜欢她呢
He really seems into her.
我拍了一段影片
I took a video.
我都忘了这事有多好玩
I forgot how much fun this is.
好了  我们看见他们了
Okay, we saw them.
我们可以去看电影了吗
Can we go catch the movie?
你为什么要带他来
Why'd you bring him?
没办法啊  我俩被一纸婚书捆绑了
I had to; we're married now.
老娘感同身受啊
Ugh, I hear that.
抱歉  让我再问最后一个关于谢尔顿的问题
I'm sorry, just one more question about Sheldon.
好吧  问吧
Sure, why not?
其实这个问题分为四个小题
It's more of a four-part question, really.
他撰写超奇异质数的论文时
When he wrote his paper on supersingular prime numbers,
花了多长时间
how long did it take?
大概一个半小时吧
Um... about an hour and half.
哇  我的亲娘呀
I mean, wow!
你亲眼目睹了吗
And you were there to see it?
是的  我们当时正在外面约会
Yes. Yep. We were on a date.
跟现在情况差不多
Very much like this one.
我对此深表怀疑
I doubt it was like this one.
他可是个大天才
I mean, he's a genius,
而我的智商低到无法想通
and I wasn't even smart enough to figure out
为什么我老婆闻起来总是一股牛角面包味
why my wife always smelled of croissants.
你剩下的问题是什么
What was the rest of your question?
你可以把我介绍给他吗
Do you think you could introduce me to him?
你说真的吗
Really?
你想让我介绍我的前男友给你认识吗
You-you want me to introduce you to my ex-boyfriend?
你说得对  这太诡异了
You're right, it's-it's weird.
不  等等  就这么做吧
No, wait. Do it.
不  我改变主意了
No. I changed my mind.
我一定会紧张死的
I'd be too nervous.
我不知该如何是好了
Oh! I don't know what to do.
我们还要待多久
Are we gonna be much longer?
我要上厕所了
I really have to go to the bathroom.
早有准备
Right here.
离最后期限还差37分钟
37 minutes left until the deadline.
会有人出现的
Someone will show.
不管最后结果如何
And no matter what happens,
这都将是一个好玩的实验
this is still a fun experiment.
肯定比不上那晚用微波炉爆葡萄好玩
Not as fun as the night we blew up grapes in the microwave.
我们的确活得很精彩啊
We really have led full lives.
会有人会出现的
Someone will show.
也许你不想要和你完全一样的人
Maybe you don't want someone exactly like you.
你知道大家都说  异性相吸
You know what they say: opposites attract.
照这个逻辑来说
Well, by that logic,
那我是该找个又矮又无聊又黏人的那种吗
I should be with someone short, dull and needy, eh?
我不是故意要吐槽
Not to cast aspersions,
不过我在这儿一挥手  就能打中几个这样的人呢
but I can't shake a stick around here without hitting that.
我曾经驾车500英里
You know, I once drove 500 miles
只为了聆听他在斯坦福演讲
to hear him speak at Stanford.
我有那堂课的DVD
I have a DVD of that lecture.
真的吗  是不是特别棒
Really? Wasn't it great?
作为情人节的礼物  一点都不棒
Not as a Valentine's present, no.
下次你再看那张碟时
Well, the next time you watch it,
我就是那个提问题被他评为
I'm the bloke who asked the question
又蠢又傻的那个小子
that he said was stupid and obvious.
那是他对在场人士说的最友善的话了
It was the nicest thing he said to anyone there.
那还真是厉害
That's, um, terrific.
我有点累了  今晚先这样好吗
Listen, I'm-I'm kind of tired. Can we call it a night?
哎呀  对不起  我一整晚都在
Oh, gosh. Sorry, I've just spent the whole night
谈论你的前男友
talking about your ex-boyfriend.
我真是个大傻瓜
I'm such an idiot.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
也许还不算是傻瓜  但肯定不如
Well, maybe not an idiot, but certainly not as smart as...
那个不能提的人聪明
someone we won't mention.
谢谢
Thank you.
但你说了你也许会把我介绍给他
But you said you might introduce me to him--
我周四有空哦
I'm free on Thursday.
他们要起身离开了
Hey, hey, they're leaving.
什么  给我  给我
What? Here, give me, give me.
天啊  天啊  他们正向我们走来
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, they're coming right towards us.
我们得赶紧离开
We got to get out of here.
好的  等等  莱纳德怎么办
Okay. Well, wait, what about Leonard?
他和他的小膀胱可以去搭巴士
He and his tiny bladder can take the bus!
不是吧
Oh, no!
她把我的车给撞了
She just hit my car!
你们怎么在这里
What are you guys doing here?
好啊  艾米  你怎么在这呢
Oh! Hey, Ames! What are you doing here?
怎么回事
What happened?
老天爷
Omg!
您不是莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德吧
Aren't you Leonard Hofstadter?
是
Yeah.
我看过你在斯坦福跟谢尔顿一起演讲
I saw you speak at Stanford with Sheldon Cooper!
艾米  你相信吗
Amy, can you believe it?
这居然是莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德博士
It's Dr. Leonard Hofstadter!
不相信  快把我从梦中捏醒
No. Pinch me.
见到你真是太高兴了  能握个手吗
It's an absolute pleasure to meet you. Can I shake your hand?
不知道你愿不愿意  我才刚刚
I don't know if you want to do that-- I was just...
好吧  当我没说
Okay, never mind.
艾米  我这辈子再也不洗这只手了
Amy, I'm never washing this hand again.
你应该好好洗
You really should.
60秒
60 seconds.
这可不妙
This is not looking good.
一分钟足够长了
One minute is a long time.
这句话我跟女人说了二十年
I've been telling women that for 20 years.
45秒
45.
45秒足够一个女人
45 seconds is plenty of time for a woman
走进那扇门  然后爱上我了
to walk through that door and fall in love with me.
要是用上我这双星星眼  时间还要减半呢
You know, probably half that if I break out the old cow eyes.
30秒
30 seconds.
万一是詹妮弗·劳伦斯呢
What if it's Jennifer Lawrence?
什么
What?
上一部《饥饿游戏》可不是我的菜
Oh, that last  Hunger Games was not my cup of tea.
你不是说她在《X战警》里演得特别好吗
You thought she was great in X-Men.
好吧  我不会拒绝詹妮弗·劳伦斯的
Oh, fine-- I won't shut my heart to the love of Jennifer Lawrence.
各位  15秒了
Guys, 15 seconds.
也许她是等着最后一刻出场呢
Maybe she's waiting to show up at the last possible moment.
听起来好爱演的事儿精女生
Sounds like a drama queen.
不  还真是詹妮弗·劳伦斯啊
Oh, no. It is Jennifer Lawrence.
Five...
four...
three...
two...
one.
太糟了
That's too bad.
可能我们把题出得太难了
Maybe we did make the test too difficult.
我觉得这不重要  听着  谢尔顿
I don't think it matters. Look, Sheldon,
我相信命里有时终须有
I believe when the time is right for you to meet someone,
命里无时莫强求  好吗
it'll just happen. Okay?
不能因为一场测试或某个网站
Not because of a test or a Web site,
而是因为...
but because...
我们是梦想中的梦想者
We are the dreamers of dreams!
真是个姑娘  还很漂亮
It's an actual girl, and she's really pretty.
快开门啊
Answer it!
好的
All right.
有什么需要帮忙的吗
Can I help you?
你是分类广告网站上登广告的物理学家吗
Um, a-are you the physicist that placed the ad on Craigslist?
是的
Yes.
你好  我叫温妮沙·班尼特
Hi. I'm Vanessa Bennett.
抱歉这么久才来
Sorry it took a while for me to get here.
我在听无聊的原子光谱学讲座
I was stuck in this boring symposium
想走又走不了  直到看到了你的广告
on atomic spectroscopy when I came across your ad,
真是拯救了我这无聊的一夜
and it saved my night.
那些题非常有趣
The puzzles were... were really fun.
我还从来没有把克林贡语
I've never had to translate Klingon
翻译成古梵文呢
into ancient Sanskrit before.
小心  很容易上瘾的
Well... careful, hmm, it's addictive.
[克林贡语]
Chija''e'vlKub je.
或者用梵文说是
Or, as they say in Sanskrit...
[梵文]
Ahm asman matey-bee ta-teyva.
你看吧  你中了克林贡语译梵文的毒
And just like that, you're a Klingon-Sanskrit junkie.
总之我觉得必须见见这位
Anyway, I-I just... I knew I had to meet the person
想出如此绝妙点子的人
responsible for such a brilliant idea.
毕竟不用我说你也知道  这世上很少有
And I don't need to tell you, there aren't a lot of men
同样热爱物理学  古代语言和旗帜的人
who love physics, archaic languages and flags of the world.
我也算凤毛麟角的人物了
I am a bit of a unicorn.
你确实是一位特别的姑娘
Well, you certainly seem like a special lady,
但你也知道  你错过最后期限了
uh, but as you know, you missed the deadline,
所以谢谢参与
so thanks for playing.
你怎么能就这么赶她走了
How could you send her away?!
她来晚了
She was late.
而且她居然说原子光谱学无聊
And...she found atomic spectroscopy boring.
用你们的生殖器我也不想和她交配
Well, I wouldn't coitus her with your genitals.
谢谢你送我回家
Uh, thanks for driving me home.
不用客气
No problem.
很抱歉你的车被撞坏了
I'm really sorry about your car.
没关系的
Oh, it's all right.
如果你下周末有空  我很愿意再约你出来
If you're free next weekend, I'd love to take you out again.
听着  你是个好人
Um... listen, you're a really nice guy,
但我觉得我们不适合
but I just... I don't think this is working out.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
非常抱歉
I'm...I'm really sorry.
没事  至少我是被
No, it's... at least the same woman
拒绝过谢尔顿·库珀的女人给拒绝了
that rejected Sheldon Cooper rejected me.
那好吧
There you go.
等我见到他了  这就是我们的共同点
If I ever do meet him, we'll have that in common.
当然了
Sure. Heh.
而且他亲过你  我也亲过你
And... he's kissed you and I've kissed you,
如果仔细一想...
so if you think about it...
行了  滚吧
Okay, get out.